Forty years of change. One enduring love.
Ethel & Ernest is a animation, drama, war film directed by Roger Mainwood.
This hand drawn animated film, based on the award winning graphic novel by Raymond Briggs, is an intimate and affectionate
depiction of the life and times of his parents, two ordinary Londoners living through extraordinary events.
Ernest Briggs (voice), played by Jim Broadbent.
Ethel Briggs (voice), played by Brenda Blethyn.
Raymond Briggs (voice), played by Luke Treadaway.
Middle Aged Doctor (voice), played by Roger Allam.
Lady of the House (voice), played by Virginia McKenna.
Detective Sergeant Burnley (voice), played by Peter Wight.
Ethel & Ernest is a 2016 British animated
biographical film directed by Roger Mainwood.
The film is based on the 1998 graphic memoir of the same name written by Raymond Briggs, and follows Briggs'
parents, Ethel and Ernest, through their period of marriage from the 1920s to their deaths in the 1970s.
It was broadcast on television on BBC One on 28 December 2016.
The film explores themes of london, england, married
couple, adult animation, illustration.
The tone is emotional.